Downtown Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Notebooks, 1835, 1874, circa 1880-1969, undated, Series 3:; (Boxes 28-59; 32.5 linear ft.; Reels 5558-5603)
  - Artist Notebooks, 1835, 1874, circa 1880-1969, undated, 3.2:
    - Marin, John, undated, 1888-1969, (16 of 17) (Reel 5581 (Box 42), Frame 402-602)
    - Marin, John, undated, 1888-1969, (17 of 17) (Reel 5581 (Box 42), Frame 603-816)
    - Maroger, Jacques, 1948 (Reel 5581 (Box 44), Frame 817-819)
    - Meigs, Walter, undated, 1950-1967 (Reel 5581 (Box 44), Frame 820-869)
    - Meurer, C. A., 1906 (Reel 5581 (Box 44), Frame 870-871)
    - Millman, Edward, undated, 1948-1954 (Reel 5581 (Box 44), Frame 872-884)
    - Mintz, Harry, 1954 (Reel 5581 (Box 44), Frame 885-887)
    - Moore, Henry, undated, 1955 (Reel 5581 (Box 44), Frame 888-890)
    - Morris, George L. K., undated, 1929-1969, (1 of 3) (Reel 5581 (Box 44), Frame 891-1135)
    - Morris, George L. K., undated, 1929-1969, (2 of 3) (Reel 5582 (Box 44), Frame 6-181)
    - Morris, George L. K., undated, 1929-1969, (3 of 3) (Reel 5582 (Box 44), Frame 182-380)
    - Nadelman, Elie, undated, 1918-1967 (Reel 5582 (Box 44), Frame 381-392)
    - Nakian, Reuben, undated, 1930-1968 (Reel 5582 (Box 44), Frame 393-493)
    - Napoli, Giuseppe, 1959-1970 (Reel 5582 (Box 44), Frame 494-496)
    - Narotzky, Norman, 1956-1962 (Reel 5582 (Box 44), Frame 497-500)
    - Norris, Ben, 1958 (Reel 5582 (Box 44), Frame 501-504)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, undated, 1914-1972, (1 of 11) (Reel 5582 (Box 44), Frame 505-665)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, undated, 1914-1972, (2 of 11) (Reel 5582 (Box 45), Frame 666-827)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, undated, 1914-1972, (3 of 11) (Reel 5582 (Box 45), Frame 828-989)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, undated, 1914-1972, (4 of 11) (Reel 5582 (Box 45), Frame 990-1143)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, n.d, 1914-1972, (5 of 11) (Reel 5583 (Box 45), Frame 6-199)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, n.d, 1914-1972, (6 of 11) (Reel 5583 (Box 45), Frame 200-399)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, n.d, 1914-1972, (7 of 11) (Reel 5583 (Box 45), Frame 400-599)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, n.d, 1914-1972, (8 of 11) (Reel 5583 (Box 45), Frame 600-800)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, n.d, 1914-1972, (9 of 11) (Reel 5583 (Box 45), Frame 801-1003)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, undated, 1914-1972, (10 of 11) (Reel 5584 (Box 45), Frame 6-130)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, undated, 1914-1972, (11 of 11) (Reel 5584 (Box 45), Frame 131-260)
    - Orozco, José Clemente, undated, 1929 (Reel 5584 (Box 45), Frame 261-268)
    - Osborn, Robert Chesley, undated, 1959-1968, (1 of 2) (Reel 5584 (Box 45), Frame 269-446)
    - Osborn, Robert Chesley, undated, 1959-1968, (2 of 2) (Reel 5584 (Box 46), Frame 447-622)
    - Oscar, Charles, 1950-1952 (Reel 5584 (Box 46), Frame 623-632)
    - Ottesen, Frederik L., 1963-1968 (Reel 5584 (Box 46), Frame 633-652)
    - Pascin, Jules, undated, 1917-1967 (Reel 5584 (Box 46), Frame 653-801)
    - Pattison, Abbott, undated, 1950-1972, (1 of 3) (Reel 5584 (Box 46), Frame 802-911)
    - Pattison, Abbott, undated, 1950-1972, (2 of 3) (Reel 5584 (Box 46), Frame 912-1021)
    - Pattison, Abbott, undated, 1950-1972, (3 of 3) (Reel 5584 (Box 46), Frame 1022-1127)
    - Phillips, James Duncan, 1956 (Reel 5584 (Box 46), Frame 1128-1130)
    - Pippin, Horace, undated, 1941-1966 (Reel 5585 (Box 46), Frame 6-150)
    - Pollet, Joseph, undated, 1928-1936 (Reel 5585 (Box 46), Frame 151-230)
    - Prendergast, Maurice, 1955 (Reel 5585 (Box 46), Frame 231-233)
    - Prestopino, Gregorio, undated, 1938 (Reel 5585 (Box 46), Frame 234-239)
    - Preusser, Robert, 1946-1953 (Reel 5585 (Box 46), Frame 240-267)
    - Price, C. S., undated, 1906-1968 (Reel 5585 (Box 46), Frame 268-349)
    - Rattner, Abraham, undated, 1921-1968, (1 of 7) (Reel 5585 (Box 47), Frame 350-534)
    - Rattner, Abraham, undated, 1921-1968, (2 of 7) (Reel 5585 (Box 47), Frame 535-720)
    - Rattner, Abraham, undated, 1921-1968, (3 of 7) (Reel 5585 (Box 47), Frame 721-905)
    - Rattner, Abraham, undated, 1921-1968, (4 of 7) (Reel 5585 (Box 47), Frame 906-1091)
    - Rattner, Abraham, undated, 1921-1968, (5 of 7) (Reel 5585 (Box 47), Frame 1092-1269)
    - Rattner, Abraham, undated, 1921-1968, (6 of 7) (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 6-133)
    - Rattner, Abraham, undated, 1921-1968, (7 of 7) (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 134-266)
    - Reiss, Wallace, 1951-1952 (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 267-283)
    - Russell, Morgan, 1969 (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 284-286)
    - Schlecter, Johann, 1960-1969 (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 287-291)
    - Schmidt, Katherine, 1934-1961 (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 292-348)
    - Schnakenberg, Henry Ernest, 1971 (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 349-351)
    - Severini, Gino, 1949 (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 352-354)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (1 of 20) (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 355-528)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (2 of 20) (Reel 5586 (Box 47), Frame 529-704)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (3 of 20) (Reel 5586 (Box 48), Frame 705-877)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (4 of 20) (Reel 5586 (Box 48), Frame 878-1051)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (5 of 20) (Reel 5586 (Box 48), Frame 1052-1227)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (6 of 20) (Reel 5587 (Box 48), Frame 6-192)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (7 of 20) (Reel 5587 (Box 48), Frame 193-386)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (8 of 20) (Reel 5587 (Box 48), Frame 387-579)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (9 of 20) (Reel 5587 (Box 48), Frame 580-772)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (10 of 20) (Reel 5587 (Box 48), Frame 773-965)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (11 of 20) (Reel 5587 (Box 48), Frame 966-1156)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (12 of 20) (Reel 5588 (Box 48), Frame 6-193)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (13 of 20) (Reel 5588 (Box 49), Frame 194-379)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (14 of 20) (Reel 5588 (Box 49), Frame 380-566)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (15 of 20) (Reel 5588 (Box 49), Frame 567-753)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (16 of 20) (Reel 5588 (Box 49), Frame 754-937)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (17 of 20) (Reel 5588 (Box 49), Frame 938-1118)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (18 of 20) (Reel 5589 (Box 49), Frame 6-175)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (19 of 20) (Reel 5589 (Box 49), Frame 176-364)
    - Shahn, Ben, undated, 1922-1968, (20 of 20) (Reel 5589 (Box 49), Frame 365-523)
    - Sheeler, Charles, undated, 1904-1972, (1 of 8) (Reel 5589 (Box 49), Frame 524-687)
    - Sheeler, Charles, undated, 1904-1972, (2 of 8) (Reel 5589 (Box 49), Frame 688-849)
    - Sheeler, Charles, undated, 1904-1972, (3 of 8) (Reel 5589 (Box 50), Frame 850-1009)
    - Sheeler, Charles, undated, 1904-1972, (4 of 8) (Reel 5589 (Box 50), Frame 1010-1163)
    - Sheeler, Charles, undated, 1904-1972, (5 of 8) (Reel 5590 (Box 50), Frame 6-213)
    - Sheeler, Charles, undated, 1904-1972, (6 of 8) (Reel 5590 (Box 50), Frame 214-423)
    - Sheeler, Charles, undated, 1904-1972, (7 of 8) (Reel 5590 (Box 50), Frame 424-636)
    - Sheeler, Charles, undated, 1904-1972, (8 of 8) (Reel 5590 (Box 50), Frame 637-851)
    - Sherbell, Rhoda, 1933-1964 (Reel 5590 (Box 50), Frame 852-861)
    - Siporin, Mitchell, undated, 1937-1968, (1 of 3) (Reel 5590 (Box 50), Frame 862-975)
    - Siporin, Mitchell, undated, 1937-1968, (2 of 3) (Reel 5590 (Box 51), Frame 976-1085)
    - Siporin, Mitchell, undated, 1937-1968, (3 of 3) (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 6-181)
    - Sloan, John, 1957-1963 (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 182-184)
    - Smith, John, 1937-1938 (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 185-190)
    - Spencer, Niles, undated, circa 1915-1968, (1 of 2) (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 191-378)
    - Spencer, Niles, undated, circa 1915-1968, (2 of 2) (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 379-564)
    - Spruance, Benton, 1935 (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 565-568)
    - Stamos, Theodoros, 1922-1964 (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 569-573)
    - Stasack, Edward, undated, 1955-1969, (1 of 2) (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 574-718)
    - Stasack, Edward, undated, 1955-1969, (2 of 2) (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 719-861)
    - Steig, Joseph, undated, 1935-1937 (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 862-874)
    - Steig, William, undated, 1939-1948 (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 875-1047)
    - Steinberg, Saul, 1948, 1964 (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 1048-1050)
    - Stella, Joseph, undated, 1910-1972 (Reel 5591 (Box 51), Frame 1051-1206)
    - Stenvall, John F., undated, 1937-1939 (Reel 5592 (Box 51), Frame 6-29)
    - Stieglitz, Alfred, undated, 1905-1958, (1 of 2) (Reel 5592 (Box 51), Frame 30-222)
      (also includes artists once represented by him)
    - Stieglitz, Alfred (2 of 2), undated, 1905-1958, (2 of 2) (Reel 5592 (Box 51), Frame 223-420)
    - Storrs, John H., undated, 1913-1972, (1 of 3) (Reel 5592 (Box 51), Frame 421-560)
    - Storrs, John H., undated, 1913-1972, (2 of 3) (Reel 5592 (Box 51), Frame 561-698)
    - Storrs, John H., undated, 1913-1972, (3 of 3) (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 6-191)
    - Suba, Miklos, undated, 1945, 1959 (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 192-211)
    - Tajiri, Shinkichi, 1962-1968 (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 212-221)
    - Tam, Reuben, undated, 1938-1964, (1 of 2) (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 222-368)
    - Tam, Reuben, undated, 1938-1964, (2 of 2) (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 369-514)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, undated, 1937-1960 (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 515-525)
    - Tobey, Mark, 1950-1969 (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 526-598)
    - Tseng, Yu-Ho (Betty Ecke), n.d, 1946-1969, (1 of 4) (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 599-782)
    - Tseng, Yu-Ho (Betty Ecke), n.d, 1946-1969, (2 of 4) (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 783-966)
    - Tseng, Yu-Ho (Betty Ecke), n.d, 1946-1969, (3 of 4) (Reel 5593 (Box 52), Frame 967-1146)
    - Tseng, Yu-ho (Betty Ecke), undated, 1946-1969, (4 of 4) (Reel 5594 (Box 52), Frame 6-83)
    - Varian, Dorothy, undated, 1929-1939 (Reel 5594 (Box 52), Frame 84-139)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, undated, 1929 (Reel 5594 (Box 52), Frame 140-143)
    - Walters, Carl, undated, 1932-1940 (Reel 5594 (Box 52), Frame 144-248)
    - Weber, Max, undated, 1906-1972, (1 of 7) (Reel 5594 (Box 53), Frame 249-438)
    - Weber, Max, undated, 1906-1972, (2 of 7) (Reel 5594 (Box 53), Frame 439-627)
    - Weber, Max, undated, 1906-1972, (3 of 7) (Reel 5594 (Box 53), Frame 628-816)
    - Weber, Max, undated, 1906-1972, (4 of 7) (Reel 5594 (Box 53), Frame 817-1004)
    - Weber, Max, undated, 1906-1972, (5 of 7) (Reel 5594 (Box 53), Frame 1005-1185)
    - Weber, Max, undated, 1906-1972, (6 of 7) (Reel 5595 (Box 53), Frame 6-238)
    - Weber, Max, undated, 1906-1972, (7 of 7) (Reel 5595 (Box 53), Frame 239-488)
    - Zajac, Jack, undated, 1956-1962 (Reel 5595 (Box 53), Frame 489-625)
    - Zerbe, Karl, undated, 1930-1967, (1 of 5) (Reel 5595 (Box 53), Frame 626-801)
    - Zerbe, Karl, undated, 1930-1967, (2 of 5) (Reel 5595 (Box 53), Frame 802-978)
    - Zerbe, Karl, undated, 1930-1967, (3 of 5) (Reel 5595 (Box 54), Frame 979-1152)
    - Zerbe, Karl, undated, 1930-1967, (4 of 5) (Reel 5596 (Box 54), Frame 6-197)
    - Zerbe, Karl, undated, 1930-1967, (5 of 5) (Reel 5596 (Box 54), Frame 198-301)
    - Zorach, Marguerite, undated, 1929-1968 (Reel 5596 (Box 54), Frame 302-307)
    - Zorach, William, undated, 1912-1968, (1 of 9) (Reel 5596 (Box 54), Frame 308-513)
    - Zorach, William, undated, 1912-1968, (2 of 9) (Reel 5596 (Box 54), Frame 514-720)
    - Zorach, William, undated, 1912-1968, (3 of 9) (Reel 5596 (Box 55), Frame 721-926)
    - Zorach, William, undated, 1912-1968, (4 of 9) (Reel 5596 (Box 55), Frame 927-1127)
    - Zorach, William, undated, 1912-1968, (5 of 9) (Reel 5597 (Box 55), Frame 6-202)
    - Zorach, William, undated, 1912-1968, (6 of 9) (Reel 5597 (Box 55), Frame 203-406)
    - Zorach, William, undated, 1912-1968, (7 of 9) (Reel 5597 (Box 55), Frame 407-609)
    - Zorach, William, undated, 1912-1968, (8 of 9) (Reel 5597 (Box 55), Frame 610-812)
    - Zorach, William, undated, 1912-1968, (9 of 9) (Reel 5597 (Box 55), Frame 813-1016)
  - Publicity Notebooks, 1901-1969, undated, 3.3:
    Publicity notebooks consist of clippings, press releases, exhibition announcements, invitations, and catalogs, and occasionally include photographs and notes. Separate series of notebooks were compiled and maintained for group shows at the Downtown Gallery and group shows in other locations. Group shows in other locations included shows organized by the Downtown Gallery and featuring Downtown Gallery loans, purchases, or affiliated artists. Separate notebooks were also maintained for American folk art exhibitions at the Downtown Gallery and folk art shows elsewhere.
    This subseries also contains miscellaneous publicity records. Miscellaneous publicity relating to American folk art in the 1950s includes separate sections of records for five collections that relied heavily on Halpert's expertise and contained significant artwork acquired through the Downtown Gallery.
    Miscellaneous publicity relating to artists A to Z includes the following artists: Archipenko, Aronson, Ault, Bacon, Baskin, Beerman, Berkowitz, Bloom, Breinin, Brice, Broderson, Brook, Browne, Burlin, Cloar, Coleman, Corson, Crawford, Dahill, Dole, Lachaise, Lebrun, Ottesen, and Stella. Photographs found here picture an opening exhibition of Our Gallery, Inc., 1926; William Zorach with doors he designed for the entrance to the Daylight Gallery, 1930; a plaque by Reuben Nakian over the Zorach doors of the Daylight Gallery, 1930; and Duncan Candler with his door frame in bas relief, circa 1930.
    Miscellaneous publicity records for Downtown Gallery relate to solo and group exhibitions and the 1951 opening of the ground-floor room.
    The series is organized as follows: notebooks for group shows at the Downtown Gallery; notebooks for group shows at other locations; notebooks for American folk art exhibtions at the Downtown Gallery; notebooks for American folk art exhibitions at other locations; and miscellaneous publicity for American folk art, artists A to Z, Downtown Gallery, and foreign artwork.
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1926 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 139-149)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, American Print Makers Society Exhibitions, 1927-1931 (Reel 5597, Frame 1018-1120)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, American Print Makers Society Exhibitions, 1931-1934 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 6-138)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1927 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 150-165)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1928 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 166-192)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1929 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 193-234)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1930 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 235-289)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1931 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 290-325)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1932 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 326-353)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1933 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 354-370)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1934 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 371-420)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1935 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 421-468)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1936 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 469-555)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1937 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 556-619)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1938 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 620-674)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1939 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 675-719)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1940 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 720-763)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1941 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 764-852)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery (American Negro Art), 1941-1942 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 853-892)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1942 (Reel 5598 (Box 55), Frame 893-922)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1943 (Reel 5598 (Box 56), Frame 923-956)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1944 (Reel 5598 (Box 56), Frame 957-984)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1945 (Reel 5598 (Box 56), Frame 985-1021)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1946 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 6-63)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1947 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 64-169)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1948 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 170-228)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1949 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 229-292)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1950 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 293-348)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1951 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 349-398)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1952 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 399-453)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1953 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 454-540)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1954 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 541-646)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1955 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 647-689)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1956 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 690-761)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1957 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 762-844)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1958 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 845-858)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1959 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 859-954)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1960 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 955-1014)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1961 (Reel 5599 (Box 56), Frame 1015-1059)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1962 (Reel 5600 (Box 56), Frame 7-77)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1963 (Reel 5600 (Box 56), Frame 78-248)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1964 (Reel 5600 (Box 56), Frame 249-294)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1965 (Reel 5600 (Box 56), Frame 295-325)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1966 (Reel 5600 (Box 56), Frame 326-336)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1967 (Reel 5600 (Box 56), Frame 337-347)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1968 (Reel 5600 (Box 56), Frame 348-355)
    - Group Shows, Downtown Gallery, 1969 (Reel 5600 (Box 56), Frame 356-358)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, American Print Makers Society Exhibitions, 1927-1934 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 359-391)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1928 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 392-400)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1929 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 401-403)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, First Municipal Exhibition of American Art, Municipal Art Gallery, Atlantic City, N.J., 1929 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 404-528)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1930 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 529-614)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1931 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 615-619)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1932 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 620-659)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1933 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 660-667)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1934 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 668-693)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, First Municipal Art Exhibition, New York City, 1934 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 694-825)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, New York No-Jury Exhibition, Salons of America, Inc., 1934 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 826-935)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1935 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 936-948)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1936 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 949-959)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1937 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 960-996)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1938 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 997-1042)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1939 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 1043-1046)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1940 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 1047-1050)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1942 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 1051-1053)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1943 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 1054-1070)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1944 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 1071-1090)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1945 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 1091-1113)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1946 (Reel 5600 (Box 57), Frame 1114-1125)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1947 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 6-25)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1948 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 26-44)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1949 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 45-100)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1950 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 101-129)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1951 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 130-156)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1952 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 157-178)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1953 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 179-212)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1954 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 213-329)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1955 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 330-345)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1956 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 346-379)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1957 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 380-410)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1958 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 411-476)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1959 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 477-502)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1960 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 503-552)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1961 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 553-612)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1962 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 613-664)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1963 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 665-729)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1964 (Reel 5601 (Box 57), Frame 730-751)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1965 (Reel 5601 (Box 58), Frame 752-890)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1966 (Reel 5601 (Box 58), Frame 891-963)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1967 (Reel 5601 (Box 58), Frame 964-1006)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1968 (Reel 5601 (Box 58), Frame 1007-1106)
    - Group Shows, Other Locations, 1969 (Reel 5601 (Box 58), Frame 1107-1118)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1937 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 6-29)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1938 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 30-64)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1939 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 65-75)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1940 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 76-84)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1941 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 85-142)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1942 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 143-163)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1943 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 164-168)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1944 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 169-177)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1945 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 178-181)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1946 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 182-193)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1947 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 194-206)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1948 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 207-228)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1949 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 229-235)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1950 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 236-257)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1951 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 258-266)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1952 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 267-275)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1954 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 276-286)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1955 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 287-293)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1957 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 294-297)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1959 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 298-302)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1963 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 303-328)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, 1966 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 329)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Downtown Gallery, undated (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 330-333)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Other Locations, 1924 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 334-340)
    - American Folk Art Exhibitions, Other Locations, 1927 (Reel 5602 (Box 58), Frame 341-353)